# Raj K Sahoo

07813592849

Sahooraj49@yahoo.co.uk

## **SUMMARY**

Experienced restaurant manager having effective passion relating to the delivery of premium customer service and effective working of operational efficiency. Highly skilled in managing the staff and the inventory well and good in creating a healthy and cordial working place.

# **SKILLS**

Communication

Problem-solving

Critical thinking

Time management

Lesson planning

Leadership

Creative writing

Effective team working

Inventory management

Food safety and hygiene

#### **ADDRESS**

41, Broadbent Street, OL11 3DD

## **EXPERIENCE**

### **OCTOBER 2017- PRESENT**

Working with Sangam Indian fine dining restaurant as Assistant Manager.

#### APRIL 2016 TO AUGUST 2017

Worked with Tapasya Marina, Hull (Indian restaurant) as Assistant Manager.

# **APRIL 2009 TO OCT 2016**

Worked with Viceroy (Indian restaurant) Yeovil, Somerset

## **APRIL 2009 TO OCT 2016**

Worked with Viceroy (Indian restaurant) Yeovil, Somerset

## April 2006 to August 2009

Worked with Calcutta Club (Indian restaurant) Halstead, Sevenoaks

#### October 2004 to March 2006

Worked with Viceroy, Yeovil, as Manager.

Key Responsibilities

- > Keeping updates relating to recruiting and training staff
- Checking bookings and arrangement for seating along with stock checking and ordering
- Executing rules and regulations along with taking orders and servicing.
- Accountable for ensuring the growth of business and enhancing sales and marketing as well.
- ➤ Handling complaints and issues of consumers as well

## **EDUCATION**

Hotel management BA (Hons) Global Business

## COMMUNICATION

Highly effective in communication as need to coordinate with many stakeholders like the consumers, employees, suppliers, external parties and many other stakeholders.